[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is Microsoft Common Data Service?",
    "answers": [
      "A cloud database for storing and managing business data.",
      "A tool for project management.",
      "An enterprise social network.",
      "A Microsoft email service.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the data modeling language used in Microsoft Power Platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Power Model Language.",
      "Common Data Model.",
      "Power Query Language.",
      "Power Entity Language.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the project management tool in Microsoft Power Platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Power Planner.",
      "Power Tasks.",
      "Project Operations.",
      "Power Manager.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the artificial intelligence tool in Microsoft Power Platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Power Automate.",
      "Power Intelligence.",
      "Power Analytics.",
      "Power Data Science.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What types of connectors are available in Microsoft Power Platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Free and paid connectors.",
      "Database and file connectors.",
      "Social media and messaging connectors.",
      "Standard and custom connectors.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is Microsoft Power Virtual Agents?",
    "answers": [
      "A project management tool.",
      "A chatbot creation tool.",
      "A data analysis tool.",
      "A graphical user interface design tool.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the process analysis tool in Microsoft Power Platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Power Analytics.",
      "Power Insights.",
      "Power Metrics.",
      "Process Advisor.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What type of process automation can be achieved with Microsoft Power Automate?",
    "answers": [
      "Automation of simple and repetitive processes.",
      "Automation of single-application processes.",
      "Automation of complex processes involving multiple applications and services.",
      "Automation of processes that don't involve data.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the real-time reporting and analytics service in Microsoft Power Platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Power BI Streaming.",
      "Power Reports.",
      "Power Analytics.",
      "Power Insights.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the integration of Power Platform with Microsoft Teams?",
    "answers": [
      "An integration that allows the creation of chats in Microsoft Teams.",
      "An integration that allows the creation of apps and workflows directly from Microsoft Teams.",
      "An integration that allows the creation of social media posts directly from Microsoft Teams.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
